Contact

832-671-1628 (Mobile) elishasrn@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/elishabrynston-sultzer-msn-8476a41 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
ACLS
Inpatient
BLS

Elisha Brynston Sultzer, MSN

Administrator/ Director Of Nursing at Harbor Hospice of Houston League City, Texas

Summary

Experienced Director Of Nursing/Chief Nursing Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital and behavioral health care industry. Skilled in nursing education, critical care, behavioral health, medical detoxification, medication administration, case management, quality assurance, TDSHS, and JCAHO. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science in Nursing with an Emphasis in Leadership in Healthcare Systems from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

Harbor Hospice
Administrator/Director Of Nursing
August 2017 - Present (3 years)

Clear Lake, Texas

Kemah Palms Recovery
Director Of Nursing
February 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 3 months)

1019 Ashland, Houston, Texas, 77008 and 1013 Delesandri Lane, Kemah, Texas, 77565

The Watershed Addiction Treatment Programs Inc Nurse Manager February 2014 - February 2016 (2 years 1 month) Webster, Texas

Devereux Pediatric RN October 2009 - January 2014 (4 years 4 months)

Leage City, Texas

I work with residential adolescents at Devereux Treatment Hospital.

Houston Physicians' Hospital

Emergency Room RN October 2007 - April 2013 (5 years 7 months)

Webster, Texas

RN, BSN, Certified Pediatric Nurse, ACLS and PALS certified

Shriners Hospitals for Children Critical Care RN 1999 - 2009 (10 years)

Galveston, Texas

Sisters of Charity Health System RN, Mental Health Worker 1991 - 1999 (8 years) Galveston, Texas & Houston, Texas

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2000 - 2002)

Grand Canyon University

Master of Science in Nursing with an Emphasis in Leadership in Healthcare Systems, Master's of Science Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Galveston College

ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1993 - 1997)

University of Houston

BS, Psychology, Sociology, Anthropology (1987 - 1991)

Debakey HS Health Professions

Honors Diploma, Health Care · (1983 - 1987)